const exercisesData =[
    {
        language: 'english',
        question: "I spoke to ____.",
        options: ["she", "her"],
        correctOption: "she",
        difficulty: 'medium',
      },
      {
        language: 'english',
        question: "Where ____ you come from?",
        options: ["do", "are"],
        correctOption: "are",
        difficulty: 'hard',
      },
      {
        language: 'english',
        question: "What time does she ___ up?",
        options: ["get", "gets"],
        correctOption: "get",
        difficulty: 'medium',
      },
      {
        language: 'english',
        question: "Where ___ he live?",
        options: ["do", "does"],
        correctOption: "does",
        difficulty: 'hard',
      },
      {
        language: 'english',
        question: "'I am not ____ this film.'",
        options: ["liking", "enjoying"],
        correctOption: "liking",
        difficulty: 'easy',
      },
      {
        language: 'english',
        question: "I am seeing her ____ three o'clock.",
        options: ["in", "at", "on"],
        correctOption: "at",
        difficulty: 'medium',
      },
      {
        language: 'english',
        question: "Easter is ___ March this year.",
        options: ["on", "at", "in"],
        correctOption: "in",
        difficulty: 'easy',
      },
      {
        language: 'english',
        question: "She's ____ work all day today.",
        options: ["at", "on"],
        correctOption: "on",
        difficulty: 'hard',
      },
      {
        language: 'english',
        question: "I go ___ by bus.",
        options: ["home", "to home"],
        correctOption: "home",
        difficulty: 'medium',
      },
      {
        language: 'english',
        question: "'Do you like it?'",
        options: ["'Yes, I like.'", "'Yes, I do.'"],
        correctOption: "'Yes, I do.'",
        difficulty: 'easy',
      },
      {
        language: 'hindi',
        question: 'मैंने ____ से बात की।',
        options: ['उसे', 'उस'],
        correctOption: 'उससे',
        difficulty: 'easy',
      },
      {
        language: 'hindi',
        question: 'वह ____ खाना खा रही है।',
        options: ['मुझसे', 'मेरे साथ'],
        correctOption: 'मेरे साथ',
        difficulty: 'hard',
      },
      {
        language: 'hindi',
        question: 'तुम ____ क्यों रो रहे हो?',
        options: ['इससे', 'इसके बारे में'],
        correctOption: 'इसके बारे में',
        difficulty: 'easy',
      },
      {
        language: 'hindi',
        question: 'वह रोज ____ पार्क जाता है।',
        options: ['एक', 'कुछ'],
        correctOption: 'कुछ',
        difficulty: 'medium',
      },
      {
        language: 'hindi',
        question: 'तुम ____ आज कहाँ गए थे?',
        options: ['किसके साथ', 'कहाँ'],
        correctOption: 'किसके साथ',
        difficulty: 'easy',
      },
      {
        language: 'hindi',
        question: 'यह ____ किताब है।',
        options: ['मेरी', 'मेरा'],
        correctOption: 'मेरी',
        difficulty: 'medium',
      },
      {
        language: 'hindi',
        question: 'उसने ____ सुना।',
        options: ['मेरा', 'मेरी'],
        correctOption: 'मेरा',
        difficulty: 'hard',
      },
      {
        language: 'hindi',
        question: 'हम ____ बारिश में नहीं जाएँगे।',
        options: ['कभी', 'कभी भी'],
        correctOption: 'कभी भी',
        difficulty: 'medium',
      },
      {
        language: 'hindi',
        question: 'वह ____ रोज़ खेत में काम करता है।',
        options: ['कभी', 'हमेशा'],
        correctOption: 'हमेशा',
        difficulty: 'easy',
      },
      {
        language: 'hindi',
        question: 'तुम्हें यह ____ कैसे पता चला?',
        options: ['कैसे', 'कहाँ'],
        correctOption: 'कैसे',
        difficulty: 'hard',
      },
      {
        language: 'french',
        question: 'Je parle avec ____. (I speak to ____. )',
        options: ['elle', 'lui'],
        correctOption: 'elle',
        difficulty: 'easy',
      },
      {
        language: 'french',
        question: 'D\'où ____ tu viens? (Where ____ you come from?)',
        options: ['fais', 'es'],
        correctOption: 'es',
        difficulty: 'medium',
      },
      {
        language: 'french',
        question: 'À quelle heure ____ -t-elle? (What time does she ___ up?)',
        options: ['fait', 'se lève'],
        correctOption: 'se lève',
        difficulty: 'easy',
      },
      {
        language: 'french',
        question: 'Où ____ -t-il habiter? (Where ___ he live?)',
        options: ['fait', 'doit'],
        correctOption: 'doit',
        difficulty: 'medium',
      },
      {
        language: 'french',
        question: 'Je n\'aime pas ____ ce film. (I am not ____ this film.)',
        options: ['aimer', 'apprécier'],
        correctOption: 'aimer',
        difficulty: 'hard',
      },
      {
        language: 'french',
        question: 'Je la vois ____ trois heures. (I am seeing her ____ three o\'clock.)',
        options: ['à', 'après'],
        correctOption: 'à',
        difficulty: 'hard',
      },
      {
        language: 'french',
        question: 'Pâques est ____ mars cette année. (Easter is ___ March this year.)',
        options: ['en', 'à'],
        correctOption: 'en',
        difficulty: 'easy',
      },
      {
        language: 'french',
        question: 'Elle est au ____ toute la journée aujourd\'hui. (She\'s ____ work all day today.)',
        options: ['à', 'sur'],
        correctOption: 'à',
        difficulty: 'medium',
      },
      {
        language: 'french',
        question: 'Je vais ____ la banque pour retirer de l\'argent. (I\'m going ___ the bank to get some cash.)',
        options: ['à', 'au'],
        correctOption: 'à',
        difficulty: 'easy',
      },
      {
        language: 'french',
        question: 'Je suis allé là-bas ____ pied. (I went there ____ foot.)',
        options: ['en', 'à'],
        correctOption: 'à',
        difficulty: 'medium',
      },
];

module.exports=exercisesData;